

Benjamin H. Dean

Sr Web UI Visual Designer

About

Web Designer & UI Visual Designer, certified Front-End developer, 10 years of experience in designing Websites, UIs, and Apps. Digital Marketing teams, R&D teams and UX teams. Proven ability in combining attractive design and web optimization & functionalities.

Personal info

- 🔀 benjamin_h_dean@yahoo.com
- (+33) 6 14 31 73 56
- in /in/benjamin-hudson-dean/
- github.com/bdean05
- 5 rue de Chaumont, 75019 Paris

Tools / skills

- HTML5, CSS3
- Javascript, ES6, React
- Express.js, Node.js
- Github (bdean05)
- Shopify (e-commerce)
- Wordpress (showcase)
- · Adobe Creative Suite
- Integration & social networks
- Office Pack

Languages / nationalities



Bilingual

Experience

2014 - 2020 Senior Web Designer, Visual Designer & Webmaster

Laboratoire Dermatologique Inderma, Paris - France.

Web design and development aimed at e-commerce (Shopify), creative visual design, branding, digital marketing campaigns.

2007 - 2014 Senior UI Visual Designer

Axway Software Inc, La Défense - France

User interface and visual design, user experience teams and marketing teams. B2B web apps interface design, branding graphics, icons & Uls.

2006 -2007 Jr Web Designer & Jr Front-End Developer

CFI Web Agency, Paris - France

Web design, creative design and front-end visual work (HTML, CSS,).

2005 - 2006 Graphic Designer / Roughman

Europ Cosmetics, Paris Area -France

Product packaging and poster design, graphics and hand illustration.

2004 - 2005 Graphic Designer

Lafuma, Colorado - USA

Product packaging, poster design, brochure layouts, inventory work.

Education

2020 Ironhack, School of Web Development in Paris

Upper level 6 (Bac+3/Bac+4): Full-stack Web Development, Front-end design and Back-end architecture, top-notch technologies. HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, MongoDB, Express, React, Node-js, Multidevice...

1998 - 2003 Atelier Met de Penninghen, Atep, school of Graphic Arts in Paris

Bac+5, MBA in Visual Communication/Multimedia, Web design & Print, Graphics, Multimedia, Branding, Advertising, Scenography, Concept Art.

Interests & hobbies

- History of Civilization and Technology
- Evolution of Multimedia Web design
- Fine Arts and Painting
- Aviation, Transports and Engines

